DERSU UZALA BRUSH is a japanese brush style font. The name is from 
(U.S. titles: With Dersu the Hunter and Dersu the Trapper) is the title of a 1923 book by the Russian explorer Vladimir Arsenyev.
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dersu_Uzala_%28book%29
There is also a movie based on this srory by Akira Kurosawa (1975)

The quote on the poster of this font is :
"The Fire: Man. Alive and moving. The water, the wind are Men as well. 
They are all very strong people. The most important man is the Sun, if he dies, all die. " 

This font is free for personal use olny, commercial use requires donation.

Please contatct me if you have any questions or feedback, also about the following:
- This family does not language extensions, but I am willing to create any extensions on request
- Discovering kerning problems while using 
- Or any other question or feedback. 

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.


Thank you & I hope you like this font, and if you have a chance, watch this movie it's awesome!

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772
